A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller photographs, Gubernatorial, Bob Wands, Series 5 FA458
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Nelson A. Rockefeller photographs, Gubernatorial, 1958-1974; 5
  - Contact Sheets, 1959-1964
    - Contact Sheets, 1961 January-July; D3000-D3055
      - Swear Ins - Frank J. McMullen - New Member of Public Service Commission & John C. Hart Comm. Of State Liquor Authority (55th St.), 1961 January 6; D3001 (Box 10, Folder 8)
      - Swear In - John C. Hart (55th St.), 1961 January 6; D3002 (Box 10, Folder 8)
      - Louis Lefkowitz, Attorney General in Office (80 Center St.), 1961 January 12; D3003 (Box 10, Folder 8)
      - Consumer Fraud (Macy's), 1961 January 16; D3004 (Box 10, Folder 8)
      - Consumer Fraud (El Diario), 1961 January 16; D3005 (Box 10, Folder 8)
      - Consumer Fraud Bureau (80 Center St.), 1961 January 16; D3006 (Box 10, Folder 8)
      - Attorney General location; Consumer Fraud Telephone (Albany), 1961 January 18; D3007 (Box 10, Folder 8)
      - Harbor Strike Settlement (55th St.), 1961 January 23; D3008 (Box 10, Folder 8)
      - New York State Commerce Department - Rainbow Room (Rainbow Room-NY City), 1961 January 27; D3009 (Box 10, Folder 8)
      - Niagara Falls Power (Niagara Falls), 1961 February 10; D3010 (Box 10, Folder 8)
      - Niagara Falls Observation (Niagara Falls), 1961 February 10; D3011 (Box 10, Folder 8)
      - Lake Placid Bob Sled Championships (Lake Placid), 1961 February 10; D3012 (Box 10, Folder 8)
      - Blank, D3013 (Box 10, Folder 8)
      - Rensselaerville snow bank (Rensselaerville), D3014 (Box 10, Folder 8)
      - Swear In - Mrs. Elizabeth Bass Golding, Member of State Comm. of Correction (55th St.), 1961 March 3; D3015 (Box 10, Folder 8)
      - Swear In - Mrs Gertrude Cavanaugh, member Of Workmans's Compensation Board: Wilma Rogalin (55th St.), 1961 March 17; D3016 (Box 10, Folder 8)
      - Swear In - Judge Samuel Riley Pierce, Jr. Member of the banking board (55th St.), 1961 March 17; D3017 (Box 10, Folder 8)
      - Swear In - Charlie Dumas, Puerto Rican (55th St.), 1961 March; D3018 (Box 10, Folder 8)
      - St. Patrick's Day Parade (NY City), 1961 March 17; D3019 (Box 10, Folder 8)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller and cabinet meeting, Red Room (Albany), 1961 April 11; D3020 (Box 10, Folder 8)
      - Sam Aldrich - Department of Youth Executive Committee (270 Broadway), 1961 April 12; D3021 (Box 10, Folder 8)
      - Flora Schnall (55th St), 1961 April 14; D3022 (Box 10, Folder 8)
      - Bill Rand (55th St), 1961 April 14; D3023 (Box 10, Folder 8)
      - Swear In - Commissioner Thomas G. Young NYS. Commission of Correction (55th St), 1961 April 16; D3024 (Box 10, Folder 8)
      - Davidson - Deafness Research Institute (55th St), 1961 April 19; D3025 (Box 10, Folder 8)
      - Middletown Newspaper (Middletown), 1961 April 20; D3026 (Box 10, Folder 8)
      - Middletown START (Middletown), 1961 April 21; D3027 (Box 10, Folder 8)
      - Swear In - Edmund H. Brown, trustee of State Power Authority (55th St.), 1961 April 25; D3028 (Box 10, Folder 8)
      - Jamaica middle-income housing opening (Long Island), 1961 April 29; D3029 (Box 10, Folder 8)
      - Loyalty Day Parade (NY City), 1961 April 29; D3030 (Box 10, Folder 8)
      - Sterling Forest - Industrial Research & Development (Sterling Forest), 1961 May 1; D3031 (Box 10, Folder 8)
      - Blank, D3032 (Box 10, Folder 8)
      - South Dakota gold digging shovel (South Dakota), 1961 May 2; D3033 (Box 10, Folder 8)
      - Coliseum World Trade Fair (Coliseum - NY City), 1961 May 2; D3034 (Box 10, Folder 8)
      - NYS. Mother of the Year (55th St), 1961 May 4; D3035 (Box 10, Folder 8)
      - Swear In - Sullivan (55th St.), 1961 May 15; D3036 (Box 10, Folder 8)
      - Swear In - Theodore F Bowes (55th St), 1961 May 15; D3037 (Box 10, Folder 8)
      - United Young Republicans Dinner (Commodore), 1961 May 19; D3038 (Box 10, Folder 8)
      - Gannet news group (55th St), 1961 May 23; D3039 (Box 10, Folder 8)
      - 150th Anniversary of the NY Public Library (NY City), 1961 May 23; D3040 (Box 10, Folder 9)
      - Northway Turnpike (Northway), 1961 May 26; D3041 (Box 10, Folder 9)
      - Plattsburgh housing for the elderly (Plattsburgh), 1961 May 26; D3042 (Box 10, Folder 9)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller - Puerto Rican Proclamation Group (55th St), 1961 May 27; D3043 (Box 10, Folder 9)
      - Louis Lefkowitz and Nelson A. Rockefeller and Civil Rights Groups (55th St), 1961 May 28; D3044 (Box 10, Folder 9)
      - Cloisters - dedication of Spanish apse (Cloisters), 1961 June 1; D3045 (Box 10, Folder 9)
      - Puerto Rican parade (NY City), 1961 June 4; D3046 (Box 10, Folder 9)
      - Swear In - George Dudley, Urban Development (55th St.), 1961 June 5; D3047 (Box 10, Folder 9)
      - First Urban Renewal Trip Syracuse phone operators: Terry & reporters: Press Club News forum (Syracuse), 1961 June 6-7; D3048 (Box 10, Folder 9)
      - Swear In - Oren Root (55th St.), 1961 June 8; D3049 (Box 10, Folder 9)
      - AAA Traffic Safety Poster Winner (55th St.), 1961 June 8; D3050 (Box 10, Folder 9)
      - Louis Lefkowitz - Att. Gr. reception & dinner (NY City), 1961 June 14; D3051 (Box 10, Folder 9)
      - Swear In - Ogden Reid, SCHR (55th St.), 1961 June 23; D3052 (Box 10, Folder 9)
      - Louis Lefkowitz Rally at Coliseum (Coliseum), 1961 June 23; D3053 (Box 10, Folder 9)
      - Binghamton Regional Development Tour (Binghamton), 1961 July 13; D3054 (Box 10, Folder 9)
      - Sam Aldrich and Trampoline (Syracuse), 1961 July 14; D3055 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Contact Sheets, 1961 August-December; D3500-D3527
      - Swear In - John B Law, member of State Commission of Correction (55th St.), 1961 August; D3500 (Box 10, Folder 9)
      - Labor Day Parade (NY City), 1961 September 4; D3501 (Box 10, Folder 9)
      - Syracuse State Fair (Syracuse), 1961 September 5-6; D3502 (Box 10, Folder 9)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller speaks at political dinner: Rochester Institute of Technology: RIT Town Meeting (Rochester), 1961 September 13; D3503 (Box 10, Folder 9)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller inspecting Lincoln Center site (Lincoln Center), D3504 (Box 10, Folder 9)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller honors Mrs. George W. Northup, chairman of American Osteopathic Association Xmas seals drive (55th St.), 1961 October; D3505 (Box 10, Folder 9)
      - Jewish Ladies veteran group (55th St.), D3506 (Box 10, Folder 9)
      - Newsday Newsboy (55th St.), D3507 (Box 10, Folder 9)
      - Union Label Week (55th St.), D3508 (Box 10, Folder 9)
      - American Airlines girl & Nelson A. Rockefeller w/apples -Michigan governor (55th St.), D3509 (Box 10, Folder 9)
      - Dr. William J. Ronan award (55th St.), D3510 (Box 10, Folder 9)
      - Governor of New Mexico visit - Nelson A. Rockefeller Malcolm Wilson (55th St.), D3511 (Box 10, Folder 9)
      - West Nigerian Premier - S. L. Akintola (55th St.), 1961 October 26; D3512 (Box 10, Folder 9)
      - NY City Center Ballet rehearsal (City Center), 1961 October 31; D3513 (Box 10, Folder 9)
      - Buffalo Regional Development Tour - Nelson A. Rockefeller Dr. Ronan, McHugh (Buffalo), 1961 November 1; D3514 (Box 10, Folder 9)
      - Lefkowitz campaign wrap-up show (NY City), 1961 November 6; D3515 (Box 10, Folder 9)
      - Council on the Arts Annual Report Party, 1961 November 30; D3516 (Box 10, Folder 9)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller return from New Guinea (La Guardia), 1961 December; D3517 (Box 10, Folder 9)
      - Sheldon Keck, 1961 December 5; D3518 (Box 10, Folder 9)
      - Governor Hughes of New Jersey & Nelson A. Rockefeller (55th St.), 1961 December; D3519 (Box 10, Folder 9)
      - Josef Krips - Carnegie Philharmonic, 1961 December; D3520 (Box 10, Folder 9)
      - NY City Center Ballet - "Western Symphony" (City Center), 1961 December; D3521 (Box 10, Folder 9)
      - "La Boheme" & ballet (City Center), 1961 December; D3522 (Box 10, Folder 9)
      - "Marriage of Figaro" (City Center), 1961 December; D3523 (Box 10, Folder 9)
      - Council on the Arts meeting (Albany), 1961 December; D3524 (Box 10, Folder 9)
      - Jewish ladies sacred art group (55th St.), D3525 (Box 10, Folder 9)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller Receiving plaque (55th St.), 1961 December; D3526 (Box 10, Folder 9)
      - START-Middletown (Middletown), 1961 December; D3527 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Contact Sheets, 1962 January-December; D4000-D4060
      - Legislative Session (Albany), 1962 Janaury 31; D4000 (Box 10, Folder 10)
      - "Western Symphony" Ballet (City Center), 1962 Janaury 13; D4001 (Box 10, Folder 10)
      - Knox-Albright Art Gallery - Nelson A. Rockefeller tour & dedication (Buffalo), 1962 January 19; D4002 (Box 10, Folder 10)
      - Josef Krips conducting Buffalo Philharmonic (Massapequa), 1962 Janauary 20; D4003 (Box 10, Folder 10)
      - "Swan Lake" - City Center Ballet (City Center), 1962 Janaury; D4004 (Box 10, Folder 10)
      - "Figaro" Rehearsal (City Center), D4005 (Box 10, Folder 10)
      - Republic Aviation Conference (55th St.), 1962 February 16; D4006 (Box 10, Folder 10)
      - Rome-Utica Regional Development Tour -Press Conference; Old Folks housing; VFW & National Guard (Utica), 1962 February 21-23; D4007 (Box 10, Folder 10)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller and air rights housing (St. Regis), 1962 March; D4008 (Box 10, Folder 10)
      - Malcolm Wilson and swear in, 1962 March; D4009 (Box 10, Folder 10)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller storm damage inspection tour (Long Island), 1962 March; D4010 (Box 10, Folder 10)
      - SCAD - Swear-In at St Regis; Jackie Robinson (St. Regis), 1962 March; D4011 (Box 10, Folder 10)
      - Albany slums (Albany), 1962 March 21; D4012 (Box 10, Folder 10)
      - Knickerbocker Club dinner - President Goulart of Brazil, U. Thant, tour NY in helicopter (Knickerbocker Club), 1962 April 5; D4013 (Box 10, Folder 10)
      - Chautauqua - Cattaraugus Regional Development Tour - groundbreaking of flakeboard plant (Frewsburg), 1962 May 3; D4014 (Box 10, Folder 10)
      - Chautauqua - Cattaraugus RD tour - Nelson A. Rockefeller & Sheriff (Jamestown), 1962 May 4; D4015 (Box 10, Folder 10)
      - Chautauqua - Cattaraugus RD tour -Commissioner James Gaynor (Jamestown), 1962 May 5; D4016 (Box 10, Folder 10)
      - Chautauqua - Cattaraugus RD tour -Nelson A. Rockefeller & Rochester labor management exhibit (Rochester), 1962 May 5; D4017 (Box 10, Folder 10)
      - Chautauqua - Cattaraugus RD tour (55th St.), 1962 May 5; D4018 (Box 10, Folder 10)
      - Lieutenant Governors' group- Malcolm Wilson (55th St.), 1962 May 10; D4019 (Box 10, Folder 10)
      - SCAD Swear In ceremony - Lloyd Hurst & Ruperto Ruiz as Commissioners; George H. Fowler as Chairman & Bernard Katzen as Vice-chairmen (55th St.), 1962 May 14; D4020 (Box 10, Folder 10)
      - Swear-In Whitworth Ferguson as member of Atomic Research and Development Authority (55th St.), 1962 May 14; D4021 (Box 10, Folder 10)
      - Armed Service Queens and Jewish ceremony (55th St.), 1962 May 15; D4022 (Box 10, Folder 10)
      - Tri-City Area Regional Development Tour -Clifford Anderson and Nelson A. Rockefeller (Albany, Saratoga, Troy, Schenectady), 1962 May 23-25; D4023 (Box 10, Folder 10)
      - Ithaca Odd Fellows organization; youth rehabilitation ground-breaking ceremony (Ithaca), 1962 June 2; D4024 (Box 10, Folder 10)
      - Council on the Arts NBC TV show (NY City), 1962 June 17; D4025 (Box 10, Folder 10)
      - Swear In (55th St.), D4026 (Box 10, Folder 10)
      - Swear-In - Judge Francis X. Giaccone, State Commission for Human Rights (55th St.), 1962 June 20; D4027 (Box 10, Folder 10)
      - Safety Foster presentation award (55th St.), 1962 June 20; D4028 (Box 10, Folder 10)
      - Albany Stairs (Albany), 1962 June 26; D4029 (Box 10, Folder 10)
      - American Legion Boys' State (Hamilton), 1962 June 26; D4030 (Box 10, Folder 10)
      - Swear-In - Sol. Corbin as Counsel; Bob McCrate's farewell handshake; Rod Perkins (55th St.), 1962 June 29; D4031 (Box 10, Folder 10)
      - 250th Anniversary Celebration - Saratoga Spa opening & dedication of new park & recreation center (Schoharie), 1962 June 30; D4032 (Box 10, Folder 10)
      - Floyd Patterson group & Nelson A. Rockefeller (55th St.), 1962 July 10; D4033 (Box 10, Folder 10)
      - AMVETS Safety Belt presentation (55th St.), 1962 July 10; D4034 (Box 10, Folder 10)
      - Nassau-Suffolk, LI counties Regional Development Tour (Nassau/Suffolk), 1962 July 17-19; D4035 (Box 10, Folder 10)
      - Commissioner Carter, Nelson A. Rockefeller & British West Indies man (55th St.), 1962 July 20; D4036 (Box 10, Folder 10)
      - Jackie Robinson Hall of Fame dinner, Dr. Martin Luther King (Waldorf), 1962 July 20; D4037 (Box 10, Folder 10)
      - Regional Development briefing session & views of capital (Albany), 1962 July 23; D4038 (Box 10, Folder 10)
      - State Commission for Human Rights, NY Office (missing 7/10/1962) (E. 125th St.), 1962 July 25; D4039 (Box 10, Folder 10)
      - Housing Development - George Washington Bridge site (NY City), 1962 July 25; D4040 (Box 10, Folder 11)
      - Dorothy McHugh & Ruth Washington (55th St.), 1962 July 28; D4041 (Box 10, Folder 11)
      - Swear In - Joseph Katz, Waterfront Commission Director (55th St.), 1962 August 6; D4042 (Box 10, Folder 11)
      - Jamaican flag presentation by Mr. DeCosta (55th St.), 1962 August 6; D4043 (Box 10, Folder 11)
      - Rep. Committee Citizens for Nelson A. Rockefeller & Javits (55th St.), 1962 August 10; D4044 (Box 10, Folder 11)
      - Rep. Committee Citizens for Nelson A. Rockefeller & Javits (55th St.), 1962 August 10; D4044 (Box 10, Folder 11)
      - 1st Anniversary Railroad settlement; Authur Goldburg, Mayor Wagner (55th St.), 1962 August; D4045 (Box 10, Folder 11)
      - Labor proclamations (55th St.), 1962 August; D4046 (Box 10, Folder 11)
      - Malone- Poughkeepsie Fair (Malone/Poughkeepsie), 1962 August 22-23; D4047 (Box 10, Folder 11)
      - Dedication of lower level of George Washington Bridge (NY City), 1962 August 29; D4048 (Box 10, Folder 11)
      - Syracuse State Fair - Cattle judging; Art Show (Syracuse), 1962 August 30; D4049 (Box 10, Folder 11)
      - Chatham-Columbia County Fair (Chatham/Columbia), 1962 September 3; D4050 (Box 10, Folder 11)
      - Lawrence Gerosa supports Nelson A. Rockefeller press conference (55th St.), 9/21/1962 September 21; D4051 (Box 10, Folder 11)
      - Lincoln Center Philharmonic Hall Saturday Rehearsal for opening - Aaron Copland, Leonard Bernstein; Sunday night opening (Lincoln Center), 1962 September 22-23; D4052 (Box 10, Folder 11)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller TV show - Campaign kick off, Javis Lefkowitz (64th St. TV Studio), 1962 September 24; D4053 (Box 10, Folder 11)
      - Michael Rockefeller Collection of Asmat Art from New Guinea at Museum of Modem Art pavilion (MMA Pavilion), 1962 September; D4054 (Box 10, Folder 11)
      - NYS. NAACP Convention (Jamaica), 1962 October 6; D4055 (Box 10, Folder 11)
      - Groundbreaking - NYS. Pavilion at World's Fairgrounds (World's Fairgrounds), 1962 October 9; D4056 (Box 10, Folder 11)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller press conference on Cuban crisis & NYS. civil defense - General Schuyler (55th St.), 1962 October 23; D4057 (Box 10, Folder 11)
      - Election Night at Roosevelt Hotel (Roosevelt), 1962 November 6; D4058 (Box 10, Folder 11)
      - Herbert Lobel & Nelson A. Rockefeller (55th St.), 1962 November; D4059 (Box 10, Folder 11)
      - Swear In of Hofstadter as Director of State Liquor Authority (55th St.), 1962 December 18; D4060 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Contact Sheets, 1963 January-December; D5000-D5056
      - Inauguration of Nelson A. Rockefeller as Governor of NYS. (Albany), 1963 January 1; D5000 (Box 10, Folder 12)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller Emancipation Proclamation Sunday lay sermon at Salem Methodist Episcopal Church (129th St., 7th Ave), 1963 January 6; D5001 (Box 10, Folder 12)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller message to Legislature (Albany), 1963 January 9; D5002 (Box 10, Folder 12)
      - Alexander Hamilton Bridge & George Washington Bridge Bus Station Dedications (NY City), 1963 January 17; D5003 (Box 10, Folder 12)
      - Location backgrounds at Capitol (Albany), 1963 January 22; D5004 (Box 10, Folder 12)
      - Pocantico Hills & reception for President Betancourt, Venezuela (Pocantico Hills), 1963 February 22; D5005 (Box 10, Folder 12)
      - Reception for Prince Albert of Belgium and Belgian Trade Commission - Nelson A. Rockefeller & Keith McHugh (Music Hall Studio), 1963 February 27; D5006 (Box 10, Folder 12)
      - Swear In - 3 Members of Moreland Commission to study State Liquor Authority; Lawrence E. Walsh, William C. Warren, Manley Fleischmann (55th St), 1963 March 1; D5007 (Box 10, Folder 12)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller & Guy Paschal Shaking Hands (former assistant council) (55th St), 1963 March 6; D5008 (Box 10, Folder 12)
      - Pan American building ribbon-cutting ceremony - Nelson A. Rockefeller & Wagner (Pan Am Building), 1963 March 7; D5009 (Box 10, Folder 12)
      - SCHR group and Nelson A. Rockefeller - George Fowler (55th St), 1963 March 14; D5010 (Box 10, Folder 12)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller receives replica of Dead Sea Scrolls from Youth Aliyah women's group (55th St), 1963 March 22; D5011 (Box 10, Folder 12)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller & Fred Perrotta on F. Perrotta's leaving (55th St), 1963 March 22; D5012 (Box 10, Folder 12)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller in Red Room, press conference Legislature in session (Red Room - Albany), 1963 March 25; D5013 (Box 10, Folder 12)
      - Capitol Book Pictures Legislature in Session Red Room Press. Conf.; Carlino (see also D4023-9) (Albany), 1963 April 3-4; D5014 (Box 10, Folder 12)
      - Capitol Book Pictures: Nelson A. Rockefeller bill signing Red Room 4/30: Capitol Book Layout (Albany), 1963 April 8; D5015 (Box 10, Folder 12)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller & Division for Youth Meeting (Carnegie Building), 1963 April 17; D5016 (Box 10, Folder 12)
      - Human Rights Bill Signing - Senator Baker & Metcalf; Sen. Dominick; Sen. Cooke; George Fowler (55th St.), 1963 April 22; D5017 (Box 10, Folder 12)
      - South Mall Project unveiling at Capitol - Nelson A. Rockefeller, General Schuyler, Keith McHugh, W.K. Harrison (Albany), 1963 April 23; D5018 (Box 10, Folder 12)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller bill signing Red Room - sol Corbin; Anthony Pittarelli leaves; Nelson A. Rockefeller & group (Red Room-Albany), 1963 April 30; D5019 (Box 10, Folder 12)
      - Happy and Nelson A. Rockefeller leave for Venezuela (Idlewild), 1963 May 5; D5020 (Box 10, Folder 12)
      - Swear In - Walter J. Nicholson & C. Joseph Luciano as members of Board of Trustees of NY City Community College of Arts and Sciences; also Deputy Secretary of State Mr. Abrams and Malcolm Wilson (55th St.), 1963 May 21; D5021 (Box 10, Folder 12)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller Press Conference - Red Room (Red Room-Albany), 1963 June 4; D5022 (Box 10, Folder 12)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller Press Conference on Richard Aldrich (55th St.), 1963 June 10; D5023 (Box 10, Folder 12)
      - Courtesy call on President Radhakrishnan of India (Hotel Carlyle), 1963 June 10; D5024 (Box 10, Folder 12)
      - Cattaraugus County groundbreaking for atomic repossessing plant (Buffalo), 1963 June 13; D5025 (Box 10, Folder 12)
      - Jet Airport Hearing (Idlewild), 1963 June 14; D5026 (Box 10, Folder 12)
      - Nassau-Suffolk Building & construction Union presents 1000 hr. Mona Lisa painting to Nelson A. Rockefeller as wedding present (55th St.), 1963 June 20; D5027 (Box 10, Folder 12)
      - Dedication of new wharf & terminal building of Port of Oswego Authority; Alroll plant tour & opening (Geneva, NY), 1963 June 21; D5028 (Box 10, Folder 12)
      - Building Trades Council & Nelson A. Rockefeller press conference; Peter Brennan, President of Council (55th St.), 1963 June 27; D5029 (Box 10, Folder 12)
      - Niagara-opening Lewiston-Queenston Bridge; Buffalo-opening of General Donovan State Office Building (Niagara & Buffalo), 1963 June 28; D5030 (Box 10, Folder 12)
      - Muir Report by Committee on Medical Education: (left to right) Edgar Couper, Chancellor of Board of Regents, Malcolm Muir (St. Regis), 1963 July 1; D5031 (Box 10, Folder 12)
      - Department of Commerce sales meeting Keith McHugh, Paul Miller (230 Park Ave), 1963 July 3; D5032 (Box 10, Folder 12)
      - George Fowler taping voice for Emancipation Proclamation film at MagnoSound Studios (723 7th Ave), 1963 July 16; D5033 (Box 10, Folder 12)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller press conference on Civil Rights (Hotel Dor), 1963 July 19; D5034 (Box 10, Folder 12)
      - Ministers on Civil Rights press conference (55th St.), 1963 August 6; D5035 (Box 10, Folder 12)
      - Dedication of new Long Island Railroad commuter cars; track 18 LI side Penn Station (Pen Station-NY City), 1963 August 27; D5036 (Box 10, Folder 12)
      - NYS. Fair - also Red Room Swear In, new secretary of state John Lomenzo (Syracuse), 1963 August 28; D5037 (Box 10, Folder 12)
      - Summer intern leaves- Sharon Keiser & Nelson A. Rockefeller (55th St), 1963 August 30; D5038 (Box 10, Folder 12)
      - Dinner for Nils Gellgren, Swedish Parliament member & labor expert; Keith McHugh, Sol Corbin, etc. (RCA Bldge. North lou. NY City), 1963 September 9; D5039 (Box 10, Folder 12)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller & King of Afghanistan, Mohammed Zahir Shah (Waldorf Towers), 1963 September 11; D5040 (Box 10, Folder 13)
      - NYS. Industrial Growth Conference on Retail trade. Panel discussion open to audience & luncheon (Grossingers Catskills), 1963 October 8; D5041 (Box 10, Folder 13)
      - Newsboy - Amsterdam News (55th St), 1963 October 15; D5042 (Box 10, Folder 13)
      - Proclamation signing - Community Health Week (55th St), 1963 October 15; D5043 (Box 10, Folder 13)
      - Worlds Fair-Port Authority Bldg. Nelson A. Rockefeller helicopter flight to/from NY City - Robert Moses, Huges of N.J. (World's Fairgrounds), 1963 October 16; D5044 (Box 10, Folder 13)
      - Empire Missionary Baptist State convention at cornerstone Baptist Church (Brooklyn), 1963 October 21; D5045 (Box 10, Folder 13)
      - Muscular Dystrophy poster girl & Nelson A. Rockefeller (55th St.), 1963 October 28; D5046 (Box 10, Folder 13)
      - Uniformed Fireman's Association Dinner-George Meany (NY Hilton- NY City), 1963 October 28; D5047 (Box 10, Folder 13)
      - Presentation of check by Dr. Edwards of Bridge Authority - Dr. Hurd, Dr. Ronan (55th St.), 1963 October 29; D5048 (Box 10, Folder 13)
      - Swear In - Commissioner Lawrence Pierce as Director of the State Division for Youth (55th St.), 1963 October 30; D5049 (Box 10, Folder 13)
      - Swear In - Henry W. Lengyel of Antwerp as Judge of the Court of Claims (55th St.), 1963 October 30; D5050 (Box 10, Folder 13)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller announcement of candidacy for Republicans presidential nomination (Red Room-Albany), 1963 November 7; D5051 (Box 10, Folder 13)
      - AFL - CIO National Convention - Nelson A. Rockefeller speaks (Americana - NY City), 1963 November 14; D5052 (Box 10, Folder 13)
      - Reception at Mansion for Governor's Conference on Youth (Mansion-Albany), 1963 November 14; D5053 (Box 10, Folder 13)
      - Dr. Hillaboe receives Bronfman Prize for Public Health achievement from American Public Health Association - Nelson A. Rockefeller (55th St.), 1963 November 19; D5054 (Box 10, Folder 13)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller & Governor William Scranton of Pennsylvania discuss PA's primary & delegates (55th St.), 1963 November 21; D5055 (Box 10, Folder 13)